we started working with Home Service Studios and
those guys are great and uh,
not only just on the business end of
it, but um, we've created some valuable friendships
out of it as well.
and we've just gained a lot of awareness
in the community. It's it's one of those
things I I don't really like being on
camera. I'm not flashy.
I'm not the guy that's out there,
you know, on on Instagram and just saying,
"Hey, look at what I'm doing.
Look at this. Look at that." Um I'm
just kind of in the background uh watching.
And so it's a little more out of
out of my comfort zone to to do
this. But I knew going into it,
this is where we need to go to
get our brand out there.
And so we kind of stepped into that
uncomfortable territory and started doing it.
We started getting a lot of good feedback.
We would we would get to the customer's
home and it was like they already made
their mind up that they were going to
purchase from us cuz they were like,
"Oh, we already seen all your videos.
We you know, we we read your reviews.
What's there to do?" It's like,
"Oh, well, we we still got to get
you a price. Yeah.
We still got to run through our process."
So that's been really huge.
And it's also been really huge in recruiting.
Yeah, because the technicians or whoever you might
be trying to recruit feels like they already
know the company. Uh they got a little
inside into the company and how you run
and your culture and uh they feel comfortable
making that jump because that's a big commitment
especially in a small town where there's not
many options. Uh you can burn bridges really
quick. They want to make sure that they're
making the right moves as well.
Well, you know,